Ladies and gentlemen members of the FFA I'd like to take just a minute to talk
to you about heart and I know I don't have to tell FFA members about heart
but I would like to turn it over to the heart of the band our lead tuba player
Ron Ruff
I'm Ron Ruff and I represent the Montana Association. I'm Brad Sared and I'm
representing the Mississippi Association. I'd like to congratulate Nancy Mason and
the other FFA officers, I mean members that got elected as national officers. At
this time let's give them a warm round of applause for their accomplishments.
With the tuba sections please stand up. Would Mr. Inglith and Mr. Heed please report to the stage.
As you all know we've been working very hard this last week. We got here last
Sunday our first rehearsal is one o'clock in the afternoon and I must admit it
didn't sound like too much at first but through the work of Mr. Heath and Mr.
Inglith we got a very good sounding band put together. I'm very proud to be a part
of this band. The tuba section and I decided we would show Mr. Heath our
appreciation. We all chipped in and got him this t-shirt here. On the front it
says FFA National Band Tubas, Kansas City, Missouri 1984. On the back it says
honorary director for life. Mr. Heath we'd like you to have this. Wear it in
good health. Thank you. Now Mr. Inglith he has been assisting Mr. Heath all
throughout the week and he has proven his capabilities. One day Mr. Heath had
to go to Denver on urgent business and Mr. E took over. So we got Mr. E a t-shirt
also. Same thing on the front. Simply Mr. E on the back. Thank you. We appreciate
it very much Mr. E.
Would Mrs. Heath and Mrs. E please come to the stage?
Would Mr. E and Mr. Heath please come to the stage also? On behalf of the band we'd
like to give them just a small token. It's only a little bit to express how much
they do for us but their willingness and dedication to help us has made us the
band that we are for you today. Thank you Mr. Heath, Mrs. Heath and Mr. and Mrs.
Inglith.
Hello future farmers I'm Joe Campbell from the Wyoming Association. I have a
special friend here who's gonna help me introduce the national band. His name is
Kermit the Frog. Hi I'm Kermit the Frog. Okay I just want to say I am also a
former FFA member. You are? Yeah. Future Frogies of America.
Okay the next song you're gonna hear is a popular song it's on a movie
starring Mr. E. and it's called The Thing from the A-Team and here is the
national FFA band.
The Thing from the A-Team.
We'd like to welcome you to the musical extravaganza tonight and what we have
put together is the best of the acts that you've seen throughout the
convention. The national band, the chorus and the talent acts. Right now I'd like
to introduce to you a young lady who is going to introduce the next chorus
number. We hope you enjoy this musical spectacular this evening. Holly would you
like to tell us about the chorus? We could think of no better way to start off
this evening than by bringing out a little bit of that enthusiasm that I
know is in all of you tonight. So we're gonna rise up singing.
Don't arise unscathed.
Rise unscathed.
It's a brand new day.
See the sun is shining and the rain is falling like it was just yesterday.
Feel like living.
Yes I feel like living.
Got a reason to stay.
Don't arise unscathed.
Throw my troubles away cause it's a brand new day.
I woke up this morning and saw the rising of the sun.
All at once I realized that a brand new day had begun.
I glanced outside my window and jumped right out of my bed.
I looked around for my feet on the ground and this is what I said.
Rise unscathed.
It's a brand new day.
See the sun is shining and the rain is falling like it was just yesterday.
Feel like living.
Yes I feel like living.
Got a reason to stay.
Gonna rise unscathed.
Throw my troubles away cause it's a brand new day.
You wake up some morning and the sky seems cloudy and gray.
Just remember what I said and things will work out okay.
Open up your windows and take a breath of fresh air.
Stand up proud to say it out loud for all the world to hear.
Rise unscathed.
It's a brand new day.
See the sun is shining and the rain is falling like it was just yesterday.
Feel like living.
Got a reason to stay.
Gonna rise unscathed.
Throw my troubles away cause it's a brand new day.
Brand new day.
It's a brand new day.
Gonna rise unscathed.
Brand new day.
See the sun is shining and the rain is falling like it was just yesterday.
Feel like living.
Got a reason to stay.
Gonna rise unscathed.
Throw my troubles away cause it's a brand new day.
Brand new day.
It's a brand new day.
Hello, I'm Sean Ross.
Hello, I'm Sean Ross and I'm from the Webberville FFA chapter, Webberville, Michigan.
I'm James Greenwald from the Lingaforte Laramie FFA chapter in Wyoming. Let's go, pokes!
I'm Matt Mills from the Mission Valley FFA chapter in Kansas.
I'm Ron Ruff. I'm Ron Ruff from the Belt Valley chapter, Belt, Montana.
I'm David Bridges from Florida. It's somewhat warmer there right now.
We're going to play a song called Dicks Land Jamboree.
Dicks Land Jamboree.
And next, we have from Breckenridge, Michigan, a young lady who's been tap dancing for about 11 years.
Her name is Tammy Valier and she has cleaned it up the town.
Would you have a big round of applause, please, for Tammy Valier. Bring her on.
Let's go.
The time won't back it, but the air won't disappear.
They knew that they were missing some more.
The boys and the teachers only called us Mother and Sheep.
They were the parts that taught them how to do the joys that they're fighting.
And now they're the parts that the both of us must be standing.
We're in love this time.
Oh, yeah.
The boys came up and they'd seen those books for real.
And they knew they'd get it right.
The words told them they had nothing to fear.
Yeah, the boys were real.
They were standing in the hearts, but made it still.
And they saw it back around and the whole town started to roar.
And she was standing like so strong.
She was falling down to the floor.
They were boxing and jumping and she was doing stuff right here.
And they got down to the point where it goes fast as she came.
They were standing on the top.
They were boxing and jumping and she was doing stuff right here.
And they got down to the point where you should see those spectators in the trance.
Look what's made you dance.
Well, I've been up to your door, happy now that I'm not a grown-up boy.
But if the boys had come to the rest of the cruise,
I'm gonna be making noise.
They were boxing and jumping and she was doing stuff right here.
And they got down to the point where it goes fast as she came.
We're cleaning up the town.
["The Choir's Song"]
Nanny Valier.
Next we'd like you to meet a couple of the singers in the chorus.
The gentleman's name is Alan Broussard.
He has been with me for over a couple of years now from Louisiana,
and he's also the student director of the group
and been doing some introductions.
And the young lady is from Missouri.
Her name is Rachel McDonald,
and she's the sister of Becky McDonald,
who's been with me for about three years.
They're going to be doing an Anne Murray tune
and a duet entitled,
Nobody Loves Me Like You Do.
Let's go, Rachel and Alan.
["The Choir's Song"]
Like a candle burning bright
Love is glowing in your eyes
Flame turned light our way
That burns brighter every day
Now I have you
Nobody loves me like you do
Like a leaf upon the wind
I could find no place to hide
I dream the hours away
Wandered every day
Do dreams come true
Nobody loves me like you do
What if I never met you?
Where would I be right now?
Funny how life just falls in place somehow
You touch my heart in places
That I never even knew
Nobody loves me like you do
I was words without a tune
I was a song still unsung
A poem with no rhyme
A dancer out of time
But now there's you
Nobody loves me like you do
What if I never met you?
Where would I be right now?
Funny how life just falls in place somehow
You touch my heart in places
That I never even knew
Nobody loves me
Nobody loves me like you do
The next song I'd like to introduce to you represents the entire reason why we are here this evening and throughout the week.
We would like to celebrate the music.
The song you say by melody
The song you say by words
When I hear, I hear my music
I want to sing, I want to sing with you
I want the world to sing my song with me
I want the world to hear my song
So come on, come on, let your hands with me
I got the song and you got the time
Celebrate the music, celebrate the good times
Let the music move you to the beat of the band
Sing it one more time
Celebrate the music, celebrate the good times
Let the music move you to the beat of the band
My song, never let the music stop
I want a good time
Never let the rhythm drop
I want to sing my song
Never let the music stop
Good song
Never let the rhythm drop
I want to sing my song
Never let the music stop
Good song
Celebrate the music
Celebrate the good times
Let the music move you to the beat of the band
Sing it one more time
Celebrate the music
with my song
Hi there
Having a good time?
I'm Susan Hahn and I'm from the Minnesota chapter
You've heard the band play contemporary music, Dixieland music, and patriotic music
And now the band is going to prove that it can also rock
We have two soloists, one is on the trap set
And that is Chris Pan Baker
And we have a twirler, which is Cheryl Van Luen
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight
How many of you out there like Lionel Richie?
Well, I'm sorry to say that he was unable to be with us this evening
But he sent his brother instead
I'd like to introduce to you Charles Johnson from the Indiana Association
And he would just like to say hello
With you inside my mind
And in my dreams I kissed your lips a thousand times
And sometimes see you pass outside my door
Hello
Is it me you're looking for?
I can see it in your eyes
I can see it in your smile
You all I ever wanted
My arms open wide
Cause you know just what to say
And you know just what to do
And I want to tell you so much
I love you
I long to see the sunlight in your head
And tell you time and time again
How much I care
Sometimes I feel my heart will overflow
Hello
I just got to let you know
Cause I wonder where you are
And I wonder what you do
Are you somewhere feeling lonely
Or someone loving you
Tell me how to win your heart
For I haven't got a clue
But let me start by saying
I love you
Hello
Is it me you're looking for?
I can see it in your eyes
I just got to let you know
Cause I wonder where you are
And I wonder what you do
Are you somewhere feeling lonely
Or someone loving you
Tell me how to win your heart
For I haven't got a clue
But let me start by saying
I love you
Hello
Charles Johnson
Wonderful
There is an emergency message for Mr. Stengel from Dupre, Wisconsin
Would you please report to the secretary station
Mr. Stengel from Dupre, Wisconsin
We'd next like to introduce you an act that really is one of the finest in the country
Jimmy Milton has appeared on Grand Ole Opry
He is the entertainer of the year in the Louisiana Hayride
He's from Chester City, Tennessee
Jimmy Milton and his father
Ladies and gentlemen, let's have a big round of applause for the Miltons
Right there they are
Thank you
Thank you very much
We're going to do a song right now
I'm going to dedicate this one
Narrow it down a little bit
Got any rodeoers out there
Any rodeoers?
And we'll include all people from Texas on this song
Everything that I got is just what I got on
When that sun is high in that Texas sky
I'll be looking at your county fair
Amorillo by morning
Amorillo I'll be there
They took my saddle in Houston
Broke my leg in Santa Fe
Lost my wife and a girlfriend
Somewhere along the way
And I'll be looking for aid when they pull that gate
And I hope that judge ain't blind
Amorillo by morning
Amorillo's on my mind
Up from San Antonio
Everything that I got
Is just what I've got on
I ain't got a dime
But what I got is mine
I ain't rich but Lord I'm free
And Amorillo by morning
Amorillo's where I'll be
Amorillo by morning
Thank you
And we're gonna close my part of the show out right fast
With a verse and a chorus or two of Foggy Mountain Breakdown
Had it back by popular request
Thank you
There's been a fresh contemporary arrangement made
Of tunes like Yankee Doodle, Chester and America the Beautiful
Which have been put together into a neat patriotic package
That we are going to perform for you right now
The American Trilogy by Jay Chattoway
Thank you
Now I'd like a big round of applause please for the Danville, Alabama string band. Will you bring them on Danville, Alabama? Let's roll it. These guys are good and we're going to have a little kicking music here now. You got everything set up? Ladies and gentlemen, the Danville, Alabama band, go.
As I sit here, along with my memories, thinking back to the years long ago, to the past, to hear us down in Georgia, and the sweet girl that I used to know. She was young and in love with me only.
I was good news and foolish I guess, so I walked her right out of her sweet Georgia heart, and the fact that I'm lonely tells me friends.
How I miss my Georgia girl today, how I miss the pine woods and her hot Georgia clay, how I miss the simple life so many miles away, how I miss my Georgia girl today.
Music
There's a moon shining bright on my doorstep, like I seem shiny, bright and bright, but it's cool to learn my flasco, and I shoot the moon along with mine.
Fifteen years have slipped through my fingers, I've got this night known by the sky, but I won't lose you, my Georgia wings are cold, if I don't see anything this time.
How I miss my Georgia girl today, how I miss the pine woods and her hot Georgia clay, how I miss the simple life so many miles away, how I miss my Georgia girl today, how I miss my Georgia girl today.
Music
Well, these highway 40 blue, I won't tell them off my shoes, how many days since I've been gone, I've loved seeing the lights at home, wasted time with money too, so I need to search the truth.
In the kid I had to lose, lose a little bit of paper, cause I've got these highway 40 miles away.
I wake home when I was young, told me lies are things that come, leaving fortune lies ahead, that's what the moonlight has said.
Shedding dreams of mine is done, money is ghost, I got my gun, I don't feel with bitter tears, but ain't been holding you, I think I wake 40 miles away.
Music
You know I've rambled all around, I could roll myself in town to town, with pretty girls that have to say, none of them can make me stay.
I'm playing music all the time, and fancy clothes, big climb cars, think some country boy can't use, think some land is yours, you got these highway 40 miles away.
Music
Thank you very much.
There's a message for Arthur Slaughter's of the Caldwell County Chapter in Princeton, Kentucky, you're to report to the information booth in the lobby.
Hello everyone, I'm Shanna Murdoch from the Washington Association.
In our next number, the band will be featuring three very talented trumpet players.
Their names are Mark Obertas of Montana, Steve Szilacic from Wisconsin, and James Greenwald of Wyoming.
And I'd also like to add that James is a member of the McDonald's All American High School Band, which will be performing at Macy's at Thanksgiving time, and in the Rose Parade in California.
Now I'm very pleased to present you with Bugler's Holiday.
Music
Before I introduce our next song, we have an announcement with Doug Stengel, please go to the information booth which is outside in the lobby.
This next song has been very popular for quite some time, and the soloist we have to present to you tonight is probably one of the finest I've seen in a long time.
He's probably even better than the record itself. We hope that the chills we experience each time we say these words will be conveyed to you.
Now allow me to introduce Jason Frazier, a guy we all like to call Bird, representing the Texas Association.
Music
I have an announcement. Miss Albee and Mr. Aide from Wisconsin, please report to the first aid booth. Miss Albee and Mr. Aide.
Good evening, future farmers. My name is Maureen Freeman and I represent the state of Nebraska.
As we look at our American history, we find the pride, the patriotism, and the opportunities granted us, and the next song we're about to play resembles all of those things.
We're now proud to introduce to you the John Philip Seuss's famous Stars and Stripes Forever, featuring pickle players Julie Hines of Ohio, Lynette Hess of Wisconsin, and Kanita McCord of Florida.
Music
Applause