When I think back on all the crap I learned in high school
It's a wonder I can't think at all
And when my lack of education hasn't hurt me none
I can read the writing on the wall
Kodachrome, it gives us those nice bright colors
Gives us the greens of summers
Makes you think all the words of a sunny day
Oh yeah, I got an icon camera
I love to take a photograph
So mama don't take my Kodachrome away
If you took all the girls I knew when I was single
And brought them all together for one night
I know they'd never match my sweet imagination
And everything looks worse in black and white
Kodachrome, it gives us those nice bright colors
Gives us the greens of summers
Makes you think all the words of a sunny day
Oh yeah, I got an icon camera
I love to take a photograph
So mama don't take my Kodachrome away
Mama don't take my Kodachrome away
Mama don't take my Kodachrome
Mama don't Hyme your bars so far from home
Mama don't take my Kodachrome away