A modern day warrior, mean, mean stride Today's Tom Sawyer, mean, mean pride
Though his mind is not for rent, don't put him down as arrogant
He's reserved a quiet defense, riding out the day's events
What do you say about his company? Is what do you say about society?
Catch the mist, catch the myth, catch the mystery, catch the myth
The world is, the world is, love and life are deep, maybe as its skies are wide
Today's Tom Sawyer, he gets high on you And the space he invades, he gets by on you
He's reserved a quiet defense, riding out the day's events
The world is, the world is, love and life are deep, maybe as its skies are wide
Though his mind is not for rent, to any god or government
Always hope for your discontent, those changes aren't permanent, but shaking
And what do you say about his company? Is what do you say about society?
Catch the witness, catch the wit, catch the spirit, catch the spit
The world is, the world is, love and life are deep, maybe as its eyes are wide
Exit the warrior, today's Tom Sawyer, he gets high on you And the energy you trade, he gets right on to the friction of the day
Thanks for watching!