A Monday warrior, meet me stride Today's Tom Sawyer, meet me pride
Though his mind is not for him Don't put him down as air again
His reserve of quiet defence Riding out the days of ends
And don't revoke
What do you say about his company? Is what you say about society?
Catch the myth, catch the mystery, catch the grip
The world is, the world is Love and life are deep
Maybe as it skies are wide
Today's Tom Sawyer, he gets high on you And the space he invades, he gets by on you
Love and life are deep
Though his mind is not for him To any God of government
Always hopeful you're discontent Though changes are permanent
More changes
What do you say about his company? Is what you say about society?
Catch the witness, catch the whip Catch the spirit, catch the spirit
The world is, the world is Love and life are deep
Maybe as it skies are wide
Exit the worry of today's Tom Sawyer, he gets high on you
And the energy you train, he gets by on to the friction of the day
Love and life are deep