Wouldn't it be better just to go home, dear?"
Armpitunia suggested timidly hours later. But Uncle Vernon didn't seem to hear her.
Exactly what he was looking for none of them knew. He drove them into the middle of a forest,
got out, looked around, shook his head, got back into the car, and off they went again.
The same thing happened in the middle of a plowed field, halfway across a suspension
bridge, and at the top of a multi-level parking garage.
Daddy's gone mad, hasn't he? Dudley asked Armpitunia, Dully, later that afternoon.
Uncle Vernon had parked at the coast, locked them all inside the car, and disappeared.
It started to rain. Great drops beat on the roof of the car. Dudley sniveled.
It's Monday, he told his mother. The great Humberto's on to-night. I want to stay somewhere
with the television.
This reminded Harry of something. If it was Monday, and you could usually count on Dudley
to know the days of the week because of television, then tomorrow, Tuesday, was Harry's eleventh
birthday. Of course, his birthdays were never exactly fun. Last year the Dursleys had given
him a coat hanger and a pair of Uncle Vernon's old socks. Still, you weren't eleven every
day. Uncle Vernon was back, and he was smiling. He was also carrying a long, thin package,
and didn't answer Armpitunia when she asked what he'd bought.
Found the perfect place, he said. Come on, everyone out!
It was very cold outside the car. Uncle Vernon was pointing at what looked like a large rock
way out at sea. Perched on top of the rock was the most miserable little shack you could
imagine. One thing was certain, there was no television in there.
Storm forecast for tonight, said Uncle Vernon gleefully, clapping his hands together, and
this gentleman's kindly agreed to lend us his boat. A toothless old man came ambling
up to them, pointing with a rather wicked grin at an old rowboat bobbing in the iron-grey
water below them.
I've already got us some rations, said Uncle Vernon, so all aboard!
It was freezing in the boat. ICC spray and rain crept down their necks, and a chilly
wind whipped their faces. After what seemed like hours, they reached the rock, where Uncle
Vernon, slipping and sliding, led the way to the broken down house. The inside was horrible.
It smelled strongly of seaweed. The wind whistled through the gaps in the wooden walls, and
the fireplace was damp and empty. There were only two rooms.
Uncle Vernon's rations turned out to be a bag of chips each, and four bananas. He tried
to start a fire, but the empty chip bags just smoked and shriveled up.
Could do with some of those letters now, eh? He said cheerfully.
He was in a very good mood. Obviously he thought nobody stood a chance of reaching them here
in a storm to deliver mail. Harry privately agreed, though the thought didn't cheer him
up at all.