This is a presentation of A.I.T.
A.I.T.
Only for me.
Yes, I care.
I.T.
A.I.T.
Throw second base, first base.
What a race!
What's the problem?
You almost killed me.
You've got her.
Throw another base.
Forget it.
Throw it hard.
Let's go.
That's the last one.
We must go to training.
What? It's your sister.
Hi, Alfie.
Do you like Edward's car?
It's very pretty.
Where did you get it?
How did I get it? I bought it.
Do you take me?
I have to meet some friends. Do you want to come?
Of course.
Alfredo, the training.
It'll be a bit late.
Yes, it'll be late. Let's go.
No, you only see if you want to.
As you wish.
And you come?
I can't.
If I don't prepare dinner, my mom will kill me.
Why would she get mad at you? You're her baby.
Not if I don't prepare dinner.
Bye.
What do you want me to tell the coach?
Nothing. I won't need it.
Kisses. You won't need it.
Of course. You won't need it.
3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
Very good. Give me a round.
Then we'll play. Let's go.
Hello, sir.
It's late.
I'm sorry. I had something to do.
Is there a problem?
No, none.
Then why did you arrive late?
I told you I had to do something.
You also have the obligation to comply with our rules.
If you choose to arrive late,
you won't be able to continue playing.
Good.
One moment, Alfredo.
You're the best player I have.
I need you in the team.
I want you to be the captain.
Do you know what that means?
Yes.
What?
I want you to be more responsible.
That's right.
Saturday we have a very important match.
What kind of example will you give others
when you arrive late to train?
I don't know.
Do you think it's good?
No, I don't think so.
Of course not.
The rules are very important.
If you don't comply with them,
you don't only hurt yourself,
you also hurt others.
Understood?
Yes, I'm sorry.
I agree that it won't happen again.
I'm going to run with the others.
I'm just a little late.
Hey, I'm already here.
You arrived late.
Where were you?
We went for a walk.
Yes, yes.
You know it's strict, right?
You know it's strict,
you won't let me go out with you.
No.
You know I love you.
Of course I do.
I have to cut.
It's back.
Hello, mom.
Hello, daughter.
How are you?
Why in the plural?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
Is Alfredo in training?
I think so.
Edward took him.
Edward?
In what?
In his new car.
Edward has a car?
Yes, he bought it today.
And how did he pay it?
He works, mom.
Yes, in a car washroom.
Why do you always distrust him?
Because I don't trust him.
And I don't want you to travel in his car.
Why not?
Because you're still very young.
You never let me do anything.
You left with your friends at 14 years old.
Yes, believe me, I paid for it.
I never finished secondary school.
But this is different.
I'm sorry, honey.
You'll have to wait for 16 years.
You don't trust me, do you?
Of course I trust you, little girl.
I do trust you,
but that's the rule.
And it's very important to me.
Well, maybe it's your rule,
but it's a nonsense.
This girl is waiting for me.
Teresa!
Teresa Martinez, come here right now.
Hello, mom.
Is dinner ready?
It's in the kitchen.
What did I do?
Nothing, eat.
So no one can go up to Edward's car?
No, but my sister says she'll go with him anyway.
I don't know why mom imposes so many rules on us.
She's worried about you.
Why? We don't know how to take care of ourselves.
Are you sure your sister looks in love?
Yes, she's a Nazca, right?
Yes.
And what do you want to do this afternoon?
Edward will put a stereo to his car
and I promised him to go through the sink to see it.
But I thought your mother said...
She said she couldn't go up to the car.
I'm just going to see the stereo.
Why don't you come?
I'd rather not go.
Why?
Mom doesn't want me to go there.
Mom is the same, but how can she find out?
I don't know.
Stop thinking and let's go.
I can't.
Okay, I'll see you in practice.
It's time.
The coach is angry with you.
I won't be long.
I'm sorry, friend.
I have to make a move.
That's the deal.
I'll give you the rest when you give it to me.
Okay.
We'll be good for tomorrow.
Eight and a half.
Okay.
We'll see each other.
It's time.
On the one hand, friend.
What's wrong?
Where do you get the money from?
Hey, I'm a hard worker.
Do you get paid so much here?
Of course not.
But I have other jobs.
What a luck.
I'd like to work.
What would a kid like you do?
I don't know.
All kinds of things.
Don't tell me.
Maybe he can help you.
How?
You'll work for me.
Can you start tomorrow afternoon?
Of course.
After our game.
Okay.
Everything fixed.
Thank you for joining us, Martínez.
Thank you.
It didn't help at all to talk about yesterday.
Well, I thought it would take some time.
Hurry up.
You'll talk to Fernandez later.
Sonny, you go after Alfredo.
Okay.
Bye.
Bye bye.
Bye then.
Bye.
Why?
Because we're talking about work.
How?
Edward gave me a job.
Doing what?
Handling packages.
What kind of packages?
I don't know.
He didn't tell me.
Hey, you shouldn't have accepted that.
You should have gotten into trouble.
It's not true.
Why are you so worried about what I'm doing?
You're my friend.
I don't want you to get into trouble.
Why do you say that?
You've changed.
It's not true.
If it is.
Martinez, it's your turn.
Stop worrying about me, okay?
Your mother will kill you.
I'm fine today.
Go!
Let's go, Mom!
It's late.
Your sister hasn't come back.
I told her to come back before 11.
We can't wait.
I have to get there in time.
I'll give her a few more minutes.
Mom, it's an important match.
I promised to stay there.
Let's go.
And you'll be successful.
I'll try, Mom.
But you have so many rules.
You are my life.
I only have rules to avoid problems.
Nothing will happen to you.
I don't think so, Mom.
Let's go.
Okay, Alfredo.
Leave a note and tell her we'll be in the park.
I'll bring my keys.
Please, Mom.
We have to go.
I'm moving as fast as I can, son.
I'll be there in time.
Don't rush me, please.
Good.
Alfredo!
Have you forgotten something?
Thank you.
THE END
It was time you arrived.
Are you late?
Not yet, but they're about to start practicing.
It was my sister's fault. She didn't come home.
Let's go!
Thank you.
Yes!
Bravo!
Well done!
Alfredo, thank you.
That's it!
Very good, Alfredo.
That's how you do it.
I remember, guys. Come here.
Your positions are on the list.
Check them out and get ready to take them
as soon as the other team leaves, okay?
Are you at the bank?
You too.
I'm always there.
Hey, where are you going now?
Let's see what's going on.
Sir.
Yes?
I'm not playing today.
Well, today you'll play as an entry.
Why?
You know the rules.
If you don't practice, you don't play.
You can't do it.
Oh, no!
They're the rules.
You'll only play as an entry in the right garden.
Understood?
But I'm a very good player.
This game is important.
It's true.
I need you to play.
But there are many guys who have come
every day in time.
And they get really angry.
It wouldn't be fair for them not to let them play.
But they want you to play.
And if we lose?
If we lose, we lose.
When one does wrong things,
it hurts everyone.
It's not fair.
Well, I'll tell you something.
It'll be better if you get used to it, Alfredo,
because you'll have to respect
all your life rules.
Now let's go to the attack.
Go sit down.
Okay.
Cheer your team up from the bench.
Let's go.
Are you going to play?
Just one entry.
We'll lose.
I'm sorry.
I broke the rules.
That's terrible.
They won't lose.
I'm looking for Mrs. Silvia Martinez.
Silvia Martinez?
Yes, I'm Silvia Martinez.
I'm sorry to alarm her.
Can you come with me?
What happened?
It's her daughter.
Teresa, what did she do?
Where is she?
Mom, I'm sorry.
Teresa, what happened?
Eduard.
Eduard, what were you doing with Eduard?
Listen to me, Mom.
They hurt him.
The man who was with her daughter sold drugs.
Drugs?
Is Eduard dead?
No, but his car was destroyed.
He has a drug problem.
I didn't know anything about drugs, Mom.
I swear.
We believe your daughter is telling the truth, Mrs. Martinez.
We've been watching that young man for a long time.
You'll work for me.
Can you start tomorrow?
Of course.
After my game.
Okay, everything is fixed.
Eduard gave me a job.
Doing what?
Sending packages.
What kind of packages?
I don't know.
He didn't tell me.
But they want me to play.
What if we lose?
We lose.
When you do bad things,
you hurt others.
I don't understand why you don't listen to me.
I try.
But you have so many rules.
You are my life.
I have rules to avoid problems.
Why do you worry so much about me?
You are my friend.
And I don't want you to get into trouble.
Alfredo.
Yes, Mom.
Stay with Sonia until we come back, okay?
Okay.
No matter what happens, Mom.
Yes, it's true.
Only for me.
To be continued...