A modern day warrior, mean, mean stride Today's Tom Sawyer, mean, mean pride
Though his mind is not for rent Don't put him down his hair again
His reserve of quiet defense Writing out the day's events
In the river
What do you say about his company? Is what you say about society?
Catch the mist, catch the myth Catch the mystery, catch the grip
The world is, the world is Love and life are deep
Maybe as his skies are wide
Today's Tom Sawyer, he gets high on you And the space he invades, he gets by on you
Love and life are deep
Though his mind is not for rent To any god or government
Always hope for your discontent Those changes aren't permanent
More changes
And what do you say about his company? Is what you say about society?
Catch the witness, catch the wit Catch the spirit, catch the spirit
The world is, the world is Love and life are deep
Maybe as his eyes are wide
Exit the warrior today's Tom Sawyer He gets high on you and the energy you trade
He gets right on to the friction of the day
Thank you for watching!