140 years ago today, President Abraham Lincoln stood at the site of one of the most important
battles of the U.S. Civil War in Gettysburg, Pennsylvania. A crowd of some 15,000 had gathered
to consecrate a cemetery for Union war-dead. Though brief, the now-famous Gettysburg Address
marked a defining moment of the Civil War. Actor Sam Waterston has portrayed President
Lincoln on stage and screen. Four score and seven years ago, our fathers brought forth
on this continent a new nation, conceived in liberty and dedicated to the proposition
that all men are created equal. Now we are engaged in a great civil war, testing whether
that nation, or any nation so conceived and so dedicated, can long endure. We are met
on a great battlefield of that war. We have come to dedicate a portion of that field as
a final resting place for those who here gave their lives that that nation might live. It
is altogether fitting and proper that we should do this. But in a larger sense we cannot
dedicate, we cannot consecrate, we cannot hallow this ground. The brave men living
and dead who struggled here have consecrated it far above our poor power to add or detract.
The world will little note nor long remember what we say here, but it can never forget
what they did here. It is for us the living rather to be dedicated here to the unfinished
work which they who fought here have thus far so nobly advanced. It is rather for us
to be here dedicated to the great task remaining before us, that from these honored dead we
take increased devotion to that cause for which they gave the last full measure of devotion,
that we here highly resolve that these dead shall not have died in vain, that this nation
under God shall have a new birth of freedom, and that government of the people by the people
shall not perish from the earth.